// Used https://www.convertcsv.com/csv-to-json.htm
const LEAVES = [
 {   "path_code": '11111',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Coffea arabica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '11112',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Ilex paraguariensis",   "suffix_text": "Isn’t it lovely?",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '11113',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Camellia sinensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '11121',   "prefix_text": "Oh, yes, this is:",   "species_name": "Zingiber officinale",   "suffix_text": "Very warming.",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '11122',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Hemidesmus indicus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '11123',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Curcuma Longa",   "suffix_text": "Lovely color.",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '11131',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Cinnamomum verum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '11132',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Theobroma cacao",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '11133',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Citrus australasica",   "suffix_text": "Not very common, yet.",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '11211',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Malus domestica ‘Crimson King’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '11212',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Malus domestica ‘Slack-ma-Girdle’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '11213',   "prefix_text": "Ah, this plant is:",   "species_name": "Malus domestica ‘Foxwhelp’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '11221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Prunus avium ‘Rainier’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '11222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Prunus domestica subsp. domestica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '11223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Prunus persica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '11231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Pyrus communis ‘D’Anjou’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '11232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Pyrus communis ‘Bosc’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '11233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Pyrus communis ‘Red Bartlett’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '11311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Citrus x paradisi",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '11312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Citrus x limon",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '11313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Citrus x sinensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '11321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Psidium guajava",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '11322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Psidium cattleyanum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '11323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Feijoa sellowiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '11331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Punica granatum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '11332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vaccinium macrocarpon",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '11333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Mangifera indica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '12111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salvia officinalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '12112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salvia fruticosa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '12113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salvia hispanica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '12121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ocimum basilicum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '12122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ocimum x africanum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '12123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ocimum basilicum ‘Purpurascens’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '12131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Thymus citriodorus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '12132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Thymus vulgaris",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '12133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Thymus herba-barona",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '12211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Persea americana ‘Hass’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '12212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Persea americana ‘Zutano’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '12213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Persea americana ‘Fuerte’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '12221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Corylus avellana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '12222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Macadamia integrifolia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '12223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Castanea sativa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '12231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Prunus amygdalus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '12232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Bertholletia excelsa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '12233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Anacardium occidentale",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '12311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Capsicum chinense ‘Habanero’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '12312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Capsicum frutescens ‘Tabasco’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '12313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Capsicum annuum ‘Jalapeno’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '12321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Mentha spicata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '12322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Mentha x piperita",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '12323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Gaultheria procumbens",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '12331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cydonia oblonga",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '12332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Diospyros kaki ‘Hachiya’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '12333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Synsepalum dulcificum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '13111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salix babylonica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '13112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salix alba",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '13113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salix matsudana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '13121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cornus florida",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '13122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cornus nuttallii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '13123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cornus kousa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '13131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Magnolia grandiflora",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '13132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Magnolia virginiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '13133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Magnolia liliifera",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '13211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Syringa emodi",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '13212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Syringa komarowii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '13213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Syringa vulgaris",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '13221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hydrangea involucrata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '13222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hydrangea macrophylla",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '13223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hydrangea paniculata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '13231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Camellia japonica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '13232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Camellia cuspidata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '13233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Camellia amplexicaulis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '13311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Convallaria majalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '13312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Digitalis lanata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '13313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Daphne mezereum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '13321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rudbeckia hirta",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '13322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rudbeckia texana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '13323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rudbeckia fulgida",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '13331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vinca minor",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '13332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Veronica gentianoides",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '13333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lantana montevidensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '21111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium sativum spp. ophioscorodon",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '21112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium sativum spp. sativum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '21113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium ampeloprasum var ampeloprasum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '21121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium cepa ‘Red Mountain’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '21122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium cepa ‘Copra’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '21123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium cepa ‘Walla walla’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '21131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium fistulosum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '21132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium monanthum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '21133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Allium schoenoprasum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '21211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Anethum graveolens",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '21212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Foeniculum vulgare",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '21213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Pimpinella anisum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '21221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Petroselinum crispum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '21222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Anthriscus cerefolium",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '21223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Coriandrum sativum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '21231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Tagetes tenuifolia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '21232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Achillea millefolium",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '21233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Chamaemelum nobile",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '21311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Artemisia dracunculus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '21312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Salvia rosmarinus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '21313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lavandula angustifolia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '21321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Abies balsamea",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '21322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hesperocyparis macrocarpa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '21323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Juniperus scopulorum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '21331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Tropaeolum majus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '21332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cymbopogon citratus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '21333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Nasturtium officinale",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '22111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lithops salicola",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '22112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lithops aucampiae",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '22113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lithops optica ‘Rubra’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '22121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Haworthia cooperi",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '22122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Haworthia bayeri",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '22123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Haworthia emelyae var major",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '22131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Fenestraria rhopalophylla",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '22132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Peperomia columella",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '22133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Haworthia truncata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '22211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cereus hildmannianus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '22212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cereus repandus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '22213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Carnegiea gigantea",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '22221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Mammillaria bocasana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '22222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Echinocactus grusonii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '22223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ferocactus emoryi",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '22231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Opuntia polyacantha",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '22232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Opuntia engelmannii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '22233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Opuntia stricta",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '22311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Echeveria laui",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '22312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sempervivum arachnoideum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '22313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Aeonium arboreum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '22321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Curio x peregrinus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '22322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Curio rowleyanus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '22323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Curio radicans",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '22331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Gasteria pillansii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '22332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Crassula perfoliata var minor",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '22333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Kalanchoe thyrsiflora",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '23111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Saccharina latissima",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '23112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Palmaria palmata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '23113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Macrocystis pyrifera",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '23121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Nelumbo nucifera",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '23122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Victoria amazonica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '23123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Myriophyllum aquaticum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '23131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sarracenia leucophylla",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '23132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Drosera anglica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '23133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Dionaea muscipula",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '23211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Polystichum aculeatum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '23212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Woodwardia radicans",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '23213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hymenophyllum wilsonii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '23221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Polystichum californicum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '23222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Woodsia obtusa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '23223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vandenboschia boschiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '23231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Phegopteris decursive-pinnata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '23232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Adiantum caudatum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '23233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Lygodium japonicum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '23311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Zea mays var saccharata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '23312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Zea mays var indentata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '23313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Zea mays var everta",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '23321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Oryza rufipogon",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '23322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Oryza sativa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '23323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Zizania palustris",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '23331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Triticum aestivum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '23332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hordeum vulgare",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '23333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Secale cereale",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '31111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum lycopersicum ‘Yellow Pear’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '31112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum lycopersicum ‘Mortgage Lifter’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '31113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum lycopersicum ‘San Marzano’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '31121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum tuberosum ‘Yukon gold’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '31122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum tuberosum ‘Purple majesty’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '31123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum tuberosum ‘Red thumb’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '31131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum melongena ‘Ping Tung Long’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '31132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum melongena ‘Rosa bianca’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '31133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Solanum melongena ‘Black beauty’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '31211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Raphanus sativus ‘French breakfast’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '31212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Raphanus sativus ‘Nero tondo’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '31213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Raphanus sativus ‘Nile’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '31221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica rapa ‘Purple top white globe’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '31222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica rapa ‘Golden ball’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '31223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica rapa ‘Hakurei’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '31231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica napus ‘Laurentian’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '31232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica napus ‘Helenor’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '31233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Brassica napus ‘Nadmorska’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '31311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucumis lanatus var lanatus ‘Crimson Sweet’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '31312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucumis lanatus var. lanatus ‘Sureness’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '31313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucumis melo var. cantalupo",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '31321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita moschata ‘Butternut’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '31322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita maxima ‘Blue Hubbard’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '31323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita pepo ‘Spaghetti’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '31331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita pepo ‘Yellow crookneck’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '31332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita pepo ‘Costata romanesco’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '31333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cucurbita pepo ‘Patty pan’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '32111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ficus carcia ‘Kadota’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '32112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ficus carica ‘Mission’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '32113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ficus carica ‘Blanche’",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '32121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Carya illinoinensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '32122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Juglans regia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '32123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Aleurites moluccana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '32131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Acer saccharum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '32132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Acer rubrum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '32133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Acer nigrum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '32211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rubus occidentalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '32212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rubus hawaiensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '32213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rubus idaeus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '32221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Fragaria vesca",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '32222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Fragaria virginiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '32223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Fragaria moschata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '32231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ribes nigrum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '32232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rubus fruticosus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '32233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Ribes uva-crispa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '32311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rosa virginiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '32312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rosa rugosa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '32313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rosa woodsii",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '32321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vitis rotundifolia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '32322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vitis labrusca",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '32323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Vitis vinifera",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '32331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Hibiscus sabdariffa",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '32332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Humulus lupulus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '32333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sassafras albidum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '33111',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Alocasia cucullata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '33112',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Alocasia odora",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '33113',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Alocasia sanderiana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '33121',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Rhodochiton atrosanguineus",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '33122',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Aristolochia acuminata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '33123',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Thunbergia alata",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '33131',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cercis siliquastrum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '33132',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Catalpa bignonioides",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '33133',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cercidiphyllum japonicum",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '33211',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Quercus palustris",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '33212',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Aesculus glabra",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '33213',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Liriodendron tulipifera",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 23 },
 {   "path_code": '33221',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sanguinaria canadensis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 33 },
 {   "path_code": '33222',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Cymbalaria muralis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '33223',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Boykinia occidentalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 21 },
 {   "path_code": '33231',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sidalcea malachroides",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '33232',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Fatsia japonica",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 },
 {   "path_code": '33233',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Menispermum canadense",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 2 },
 {   "path_code": '33311',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Gleditsia triacanthos",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 31 },
 {   "path_code": '33312',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Phellodendron amurense",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 22 },
 {   "path_code": '33313',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Robinia pseudoacacia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '33321',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Amorpha nana",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 11 },
 {   "path_code": '33322',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Zamia furfuracea",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 3 },
 {   "path_code": '33323',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Actaea pachypoda",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 32 },
 {   "path_code": '33331',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Sanguisorba officinalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 1 },
 {   "path_code": '33332',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Securigera varia",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 12 },
 {   "path_code": '33333',   "prefix_text": "This plant is:",   "species_name": "Helleborus orientalis",   "suffix_text": "",   "image_code": 13 }
];
const BRANCHES = [
 {   "path_code": '',   "prompt": "Ah, we’ve reached the first fork in our path. To the left we have plants with normal, simple, basic leaves. If you asked someone on the street to draw a leaf, it would probably look like these leaves. To the right we have lobed leaves or leaves that are made of smaller leaflets but are still each basically “leaf” shaped. And up the center we have odd leaves… lacy, round, grassy, chunky… you get the idea.",   "left_option": "Go left",   "center_option": "Go up the center",   "right_option": "Go right" },
 {   "path_code": '1',   "prompt": "Categories are important here in the garden, though perhaps a bit eccentric and confusing. Honestly, some of the categories almost feel arbitrary to me. Ah, our path will now split again. Would you like to go towards plants that are found in food, plants found in drinks (or are juice-able, some of our gardeners perhaps over use their juicers), or plants that are not food? ",   "left_option": "Go towards drinks",   "center_option": "Go towards food",   "right_option": "Go towards not-food" },
 {   "path_code": '11',   "prompt": "Ah, plants you can drink… or find in drinks. This is one of my favorite areas. Along this path we have plants in the Rosaceae family, plants drunk as “juices” and “nectars,” and “specialty” drinks. Watch your step now.",   "left_option": "Go towards specialty drinks",   "center_option": "Go towards Rosaceae plants",   "right_option": "Go towards the juices and nectars" },
 {   "path_code": '111',   "prompt": "Speciality drinks. I’m partial to the plants with caffeine, those are some special drinks! Some plants up this way have caffeine, some are garnishes, and for some, it’s actually the roots that get used in drinks! Very special!",   "left_option": "Go towards plants with caffeine",   "center_option": "Go towards roots",   "right_option": "Go towards garnishes" },
 {   "path_code": '112',   "prompt": "The Rosaceae family. Such beautiful flowers, so delicate. From here the plants are separated by genus.",   "left_option": "Go towards Malus",   "center_option": "Go towards Prunus",   "right_option": "Go towards Pyrus" },
 {   "path_code": '113',   "prompt": "Other drinkable plants, usually juices and nectars.  ",   "left_option": "Go towards citrus",   "center_option": "Go towards guava",   "right_option": "Go towards the rest" },
 {   "path_code": '12',   "prompt": "Plants that are eaten as food that have basic leaves.",   "left_option": "Go towards herby foods",   "center_option": "Go towards hearty foods",   "right_option": "Go towards foods that make my mouth feel odd" },
 {   "path_code": '121',   "prompt": "Simple or basic leaved herb plants.",   "left_option": "Go towards sage and other salvias",   "center_option": "Go towards basil",   "right_option": "Go towards thyme" },
 {   "path_code": '122',   "prompt": "Hearty food plants, also with simple leaves.",   "left_option": "Go towards avocados",   "center_option": "Go towards “round-ish” nuts",   "right_option": "Go towards elongated nuts" },
 {   "path_code": '123',   "prompt": "Plants that make my mouth feel funny. But not haha funny.",   "left_option": "Go towards plants that make my mouth feel hot",   "center_option": "Go towards plants that make my mouth feel cool",   "right_option": "Go towards plants that make my mouth feel weird" },
 {   "path_code": '13',   "prompt": "Non-food plants with basic leaves. Here we separate by size. The trees (usually taller than a house), the tall shrubs (at full maturity, may be as short as a person), and some smaller plants.",   "left_option": "Go towards trees",   "center_option": "Go towards shrubs",   "right_option": "Go towards small plants" },
 {   "path_code": '131',   "prompt": "Trees with simple, basic leaves that are not used in food. You’d think trees would branch around here but you’d be wrong. Here we have some willows, some dogwoods, and some magnolias. Which would you like to go towards?",   "left_option": "Willows",   "center_option": "Dogwoods",   "right_option": "Magnolias" },
 {   "path_code": '132',   "prompt": "Shrubs with basic leaves that are not food. These plants can be as tall as a person or two… but not five. Which would you like to go towards?",   "left_option": "Lilacs",   "center_option": "Hydrangeas",   "right_option": "Camellias" },
 {   "path_code": '133',   "prompt": "Small plants with simple leaves that are not used in food. Which would you like to go towards?",   "left_option": "Ones that are actually quite toxic",   "center_option": "Rudbeckias",   "right_option": "Ground huggers" },
 {   "path_code": '2',   "prompt": "Ah, plants with strange leaves. Some of my favorite plants are here. We have all of the leaves that are not exactly shaped like leaves. I didn’t make the categories, I just go with what the gardeners tell me. Let’s see, this way we have plants with scented leaves, succulent plants, and plants that are neither scented nor succulent. ",   "left_option": "Go towards plants with scented leaves",   "center_option": "Go towards succulent plants",   "right_option": "Go towards non-scented, non-succulent plants" },
 {   "path_code": '21',   "prompt": "Here we are at the plants with strange-shaped and strongly scented leaves. Bump into anything along this way and your nose will let you know. Would you rather go towards allium species, lacy-leaved plants, or everything else scented and strange-leaved?",   "left_option": "Alliums",   "center_option": "Plants with frilly, lacy, scented leaves",   "right_option": "The rest" },
 {   "path_code": '211',   "prompt": "Alliums. Very tasty.",   "left_option": "Check out the garlics",   "center_option": "Head towards the onions",   "right_option": "Investigate those other alliums" },
 {   "path_code": '212',   "prompt": "Lacy-leaved, aromatically-leaved plants. Some of these are used as herbs in cooking, while others are grown for their flowers. What would you like to see? Or smell? ",   "left_option": "The more robust herbs",   "center_option": "The more delicate herbs, at least when you use the leaves",   "right_option": "The plants usually grown for their flowers" },
 {   "path_code": '213',   "prompt": "The other aromatically-leaved, strange-leaved plants. The rest of the rest. What sorts of leaf shapes are you most interested in right now?",   "left_option": "Really thin leaves but not needles",   "center_option": "Leaves that conifers have",   "right_option": "Round or grassy leaves" },
 {   "path_code": '22',   "prompt": "Succulents. Truly odd-looking plants. Some have transparent windows in their leaves! And some turned their leaves into spines! And some did neither. What kind are you most interested in right now?",   "left_option": "Ones that have transparent “windows”",   "center_option": "Ones that have spines",   "right_option": "Ones without spines or windows" },
 {   "path_code": '221',   "prompt": "Succulents that have transparent windows in the leaves. Some find them rather adorable. The gardeners have grouped them by their overall shape. What shape appeals to you right now?",   "left_option": "Shaped like a pile of pebbles",   "center_option": "In a rosette shape",   "right_option": "Other shapes" },
 {   "path_code": '222',   "prompt": "Succulents with spines or bristles. Do be careful if you want to handle them. They have distinctive growth forms. Which would you like to head towards?",   "left_option": "Ones that grow in tall columns",   "center_option": "Ones that grow as a ball or barrel",   "right_option": "Ones that grow flat paddles" },
 {   "path_code": '223',   "prompt": "Plants with succulent leaves but no spines and no windows. What next?",   "left_option": "Go towards plants that are all rosettes",   "center_option": "Go towards plants that look like strings of various things",   "right_option": "Go towards plants that look like blades or tongues" },
 {   "path_code": '23',   "prompt": "Non-scented, non-succulent, odd-leaved plants. We’ve got quite a broad range of plants up this way. There are water-loving plants, ferns, and grains. Where next?",   "left_option": "Head towards water loving plants",   "center_option": "Head towards ferns",   "right_option": "Head towards grains" },
 {   "path_code": '231',   "prompt": "Plants that love water. Up this way are the ocean plants, the pond plants, and the bog plants. Which would you like to see more of?",   "left_option": "Head towards saltwater lovers",   "center_option": "Head towards freshwater lovers",   "right_option": "Head towards carnivorous plants" },
 {   "path_code": '232',   "prompt": "Ferns. They are some of the most ancient plants and are found all over the world. Which region's ferns would you like to see?",   "left_option": "Those native to Europe",   "center_option": "Those native to the Americas",   "right_option": "Those native to East Asia" },
 {   "path_code": '233',   "prompt": "Grains. I don’t have anything witty to say about them. Let’s see, we’ve got corn, rice, and glutenous plants. Where to?",   "left_option": "Corn varieties",   "center_option": "Rice varieties",   "right_option": "Grain plants with gluten" },
 {   "path_code": '3',   "prompt": "Lobed leaves or leaves made of smaller leaves. A lovely complexity. No branches though. We have our plants divided into ‘plants that someone might eat as food’ and ‘plants not eaten as food.’ Within plants that are eaten as food, we separate out the ones grown in a summer vegetable garden. Which category interests you?",   "left_option": "Food plants grown in a summer “vegetable” garden",   "center_option": "Trees and perennials that are eaten as food or drinks",   "right_option": "Plants not eaten as food" },
 {   "path_code": '31',   "prompt": "Lobed leaves and leaflets in the summer garden. Many tasty options are here. What tempts you?",   "left_option": "Nightshade crops",   "center_option": "Root crops",   "right_option": "Cucurbitaceae family crops" },
 {   "path_code": '311',   "prompt": "Nightshade plants. Please only eat the parts they tell you to eat. Which ones appeal to you?",   "left_option": "Tomatoes",   "center_option": "Potatoes",   "right_option": "Eggplants" },
 {   "path_code": '312',   "prompt": "Root crops. Taste great baked. Which direction shall we go?",   "left_option": "Towards radishes",   "center_option": "Towards turnips",   "right_option": "Towards rutabagas" },
 {   "path_code": '313',   "prompt": "Ah, Cucurbitaceae members. It always feels like summer up this way. Which kind interests you?",   "left_option": "Melon",   "center_option": "Winter squash",   "right_option": "Summer squash" },
 {   "path_code": '32',   "prompt": "Trees and perennials that are eaten as food or drink and have lobed leaves or leaves within leaves. Quite a mouthful, if you know what I mean. Where to from here?",   "left_option": "To the trees",   "center_option": "To the berries",   "right_option": "To the rest, all of which are used for drinks" },
 {   "path_code": '321',   "prompt": "Lobed leaves or leaves with leaflets on trees that have some part that is eaten. Which trees do you fancy?",   "left_option": "Fig trees",   "center_option": "Nut trees",   "right_option": "Maple trees" },
 {   "path_code": '322',   "prompt": "Berries!",   "left_option": "Raspberries!",   "center_option": "Strawberries!",   "right_option": "Other berries!" },
 {   "path_code": '323',   "prompt": "Other lobed or multi-leaflet edible plants to flavor my drinks. We have rose hips (great in tea), grapes (great in wine), and other plants used in various drinks. Where shall we go from here?",   "left_option": "Towards rose hips",   "center_option": "Towards grapes",   "right_option": "Towards the others" },
 {   "path_code": '33',   "prompt": "Plants with leaves that are lobed or have multi-leaflet leaves and not (usually) used as food. What sort of leaf shape catches your interest?",   "left_option": "Heart-shaped leaves",   "center_option": "Many-lobed leaves",   "right_option": "Multi-leaflet leaves" },
 {   "path_code": '331',   "prompt": "Plants with heart-shaped or arrow-shaped leaves that are not (usually) eaten as food. Where to next?",   "left_option": "Towards the Alocasias",   "center_option": "Towards the vines",   "right_option": "Towards the trees" },
 {   "path_code": '332',   "prompt": "Plants with leaves with many lobes that are not eaten as food. Where shall we go from here?",   "left_option": "Towards trees",   "center_option": "Towards groundcovers or low growers",   "right_option": "Towards shrubs" },
 {   "path_code": '333',   "prompt": "Plants whose leaves have many leaflets and are not eaten as food. They have been grouped by size. Which size would you like to size up?",   "left_option": "Tree-sized plants",   "center_option": "People-sized plants",   "right_option": "Plants less than one meter tall" },
 {   "path_code": '1111',   "prompt": "We have three plants in the garden with caffeine. Which would you like to see?",   "left_option": "A coffee plant",   "center_option": "A yerba mate plant",   "right_option": "A tea plant" },
 {   "path_code": '1112',   "prompt": "Yum, roots. Which would you like to look at closer?",   "left_option": "The plant used in ginger tea",   "center_option": "The plant used in south indian sharbat",   "right_option": "The plant used in turmeric tea" },
 {   "path_code": '1113',   "prompt": "Some plants make excellent garnishes, even when they have other uses too. Let’s see, here we have:",   "left_option": "A cinnamon",   "center_option": "A chocolate plant",   "right_option": "A lime" },
 {   "path_code": '1121',   "prompt": "I love apples. Beautiful plants, indeed. Make tasty drinks. There are three in the garden. Would you like to examine one more closely?",   "left_option": "The sharp apple tree",   "center_option": "The sweet apple tree",   "right_option": "The bittersharp apple tree" },
 {   "path_code": '1122',   "prompt": "Not the most common things to juice, but boy oh boy, I find the juice of these three tasty. Feel free to take a closer look.",   "left_option": "Our cherry",   "center_option": "Our plum",   "right_option": "Our peach" },
 {   "path_code": '1123',   "prompt": "Do you like pear juice? Our three have three different skin colors.",   "left_option": "A green-skinned pear",   "center_option": "A russet-skinned pear",   "right_option": "A red-skinned pear" },
 {   "path_code": '1131',   "prompt": "A perennial favorite, these. Get it? Perennial? Get it? We have…",   "left_option": "A grapefruit",   "center_option": "A lemon",   "right_option": "An orange" },
 {   "path_code": '1132',   "prompt": "These are quite tasty fruits. The fruits come in a variety of shapes and flavors.",   "left_option": "A round green-skinned guava",   "center_option": "A small, red-skinned guava ",   "right_option": "An elongated, green-skinned fruit, but not a true guava" },
 {   "path_code": '1133',   "prompt": "Here are some other miscellaneous fruits that get turned into juice. Would you like to get a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "A pomegranate",   "center_option": "A cranberry",   "right_option": "A mango" },
 {   "path_code": '1211',   "prompt": "Sages come in such lovely varieties. I could never pick a favorite. Would you like to take a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "A common garden sage, comes in many leaf colors ",   "center_option": "A sage sold dried, can have variable leaf shape ",   "right_option": "A salvia typically grown for its seeds" },
 {   "path_code": '1212',   "prompt": "Ah, the ever popular basils. We grow three here.",   "left_option": "A sweet basil",   "center_option": "A lemon-scented basil",   "right_option": "A reddish-purple leafed basil" },
 {   "path_code": '1213',   "prompt": "Do you have time for the thymes? Heehee.",   "left_option": "A lemon-scented thyme",   "center_option": "A regular-scented thyme",   "right_option": "A caraway-scented thyme" },
 {   "path_code": '1221',   "prompt": "Amazing foods, these avocados. They go with everything! Even toast! Would you like to look more closely at one?",   "left_option": "One with dark skin",   "center_option": "One with yellow-green skin",   "right_option": "One with green skin" },
 {   "path_code": '1222',   "prompt": "Nuts that are sorta round, but not exactly round, but more round than not. It may be easier to take a closer look yourself.",   "left_option": "A hazelnut",   "center_option": "A macadamia nut",   "right_option": "A chestnut" },
 {   "path_code": '1223',   "prompt": "Nuts that are more long than round. Hey, it makes sense to the gardeners. Feel free to take a closer look at one.",   "left_option": "An almond",   "center_option": "A brazil nut",   "right_option": "A cashew" },
 {   "path_code": '1231',   "prompt": "Why do they make my mouth feel hot? Even when I put them on ice cream. And yet my mouth is always fooled. Would you like a closer look? Perhaps a taste?",   "left_option": "Tastes really really hot",   "center_option": "Tastes really hot",   "right_option": "Tastes just hot" },
 {   "path_code": '1232',   "prompt": "Cool and refreshing, even when room temperature. Have a teste yourself.",   "left_option": "A spearmint",   "center_option": "A peppermint",   "right_option": "A wintergreen" },
 {   "path_code": '1233',   "prompt": "These plants make my mouth feel strange. Try one, you’ll see what I mean.",   "left_option": "A quince",   "center_option": "A persimmon",   "right_option": "A strange, perhaps miraculous berry" },
 {   "path_code": '1311',   "prompt": "Here we have our willow trees. Which would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "A willow whose branches seem to weep and hang down",   "center_option": "A willow whose leaves are particularly pale underneath",   "right_option": "A willow whose branches seem to twist and turn" },
 {   "path_code": '1312',   "prompt": "Dogwoods. No dogs allowed in the garden though. Our dogwoods come from various places.",   "left_option": "A dogwood native to eastern North America",   "center_option": "A dogwood native to western North America",   "right_option": "A dogwood native to East Asia" },
 {   "path_code": '1313',   "prompt": "Did you know that the flowers of magnolias have many different scents?",   "left_option": "A magnolia with lemon-citronella scented flowers",   "center_option": "A magnolia with flowers that smell like vanilla",   "right_option": "A magnolia whose flowers smells like pineapple" },
 {   "path_code": '1321',   "prompt": "Such a lovely smell. The flowers can really harald the start of summer!",   "left_option": "A lilac native to areas around the himalayas",   "center_option": "A lilac native to China",   "right_option": "The most common lilac" },
 {   "path_code": '1322',   "prompt": "So many flowers! Such interesting shapes and details for the flower bunches!",   "left_option": "These flower clusters are surrounded by a ring of bracts",   "center_option": "These flower clusters form in a ball or hemisphere",   "right_option": "The flower clusters are pyramidal" },
 {   "path_code": '1323',   "prompt": "Lovely flowers. How can you choose between them? Aside from as follows:",   "left_option": "A camellia found in Japan",   "center_option": "A camellia found in China",   "right_option": "A camellia extinct in the wild" },
 {   "path_code": '1331',   "prompt": "Very pretty flowers, but don’t even think of eating them. Which would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "One with small, white, drooping, bell shaped flowers ",   "center_option": "One with a spike of tubular flowers, maybe just the right size for a fox’s paw ",   "right_option": "Has small pinkish flowers that grow directly from the stems" },
 {   "path_code": '1332',   "prompt": "These flowers look so similar I can barely tell them apart!",   "left_option": "The state flower of Maryland",   "center_option": "Like the first one, but more green in the center with droopy petals ",   "right_option": "Like the first one, but more orange, sometimes" },
 {   "path_code": '1333',   "prompt": "Ah, groundcovers. Did you know that all the plants in this section have blue-purple flowers? Which would you like to take a closer look at?",   "left_option": "A periwinkle",   "center_option": "A speedwell",   "right_option": "A lantana" },
 {   "path_code": '2111',   "prompt": "Did you know there were so many kinds of garlic? Would you like to see one up close?",   "left_option": "A garlic with a hard stem",   "center_option": "A garlic you can braid",   "right_option": "A garlic that’s a bit larger and more mild" },
 {   "path_code": '2112',   "prompt": "Do you prefer onions cooked or fresh? Or maybe not at all? I like onions very much. Would you like to examine one more closely?",   "left_option": "A purple onion",   "center_option": "A yellow onion",   "right_option": "A sweet onion" },
 {   "path_code": '2113',   "prompt": "More alliums! Such smells! Would you like to get a close look at one?",   "left_option": "A bunching onion",   "center_option": "A chive native to East Asia",   "right_option": "A chive native to the northern hemisphere" },
 {   "path_code": '2121',   "prompt": "Robust and very tasty, these can be found in processed foods like pickles and also in alcohols. Would you like to look more closely at one?",   "left_option": "A dill",   "center_option": "A fennel",   "right_option": "An anise" },
 {   "path_code": '2122',   "prompt": "Here we have delicate aromatic herbs. Use them fresh for a lovely addition to savory meals. Which would you like to investigate?",   "left_option": "A parsley",   "center_option": "A chervil",   "right_option": "A cilantro" },
 {   "path_code": '2123',   "prompt": "Lovely smells, lovely flowers, a lovely area in the garden. Which flower would you like to examine more closely?",   "left_option": "A marigold",   "center_option": "A yarrow",   "right_option": "A chamomile" },
 {   "path_code": '2131',   "prompt": "Very thin-leaved aromatic plants. This whole area of the garden smells lovely. What should we head towards?",   "left_option": "A tarragon",   "center_option": "A rosemary",   "right_option": "A lavender" },
 {   "path_code": '2132',   "prompt": "These may be the only conifers in the entire garden! Which one would you like to look at up close?",   "left_option": "A fir",   "center_option": "A cypress",   "right_option": "A juniper" },
 {   "path_code": '2133',   "prompt": "A strange combination, this category. Lovely smells and tastes, though. Which would you like to look at closely?",   "left_option": "One with edible colorful flowers and roundish leaves ",   "center_option": "A lemony grass",   "right_option": "An aquatic plant whose leaves are harvested while roundish" },
 {   "path_code": '2211',   "prompt": "Plants that look like a pile of pebbles. Plants can do so many things. Which pile of pebbles would you like to peep at?",   "left_option": "The blue-green-ish pebbles with white flowers",   "center_option": "The brownish-red pebbles with yellow flowers",   "right_option": "The pinkish-red pebbles with white flowers" },
 {   "path_code": '2212',   "prompt": "I like the rosette form of these plants, the symmetry can be so lovely. Would you like to look more closely at one?",   "left_option": "Yes, the one with pyramidal windows",   "center_option": "Yes, one with flat smooth triangular windows ",   "right_option": "Yes, the one with triangular bumpy windows" },
 {   "path_code": '2213',   "prompt": "Here we have other plants with transparent windows. So fascinating! Which do you find most fascinating?",   "left_option": "The one that looks like little fingers or toes",   "center_option": "The one that has leaves that look mostly like leaves, but the plant is a column ",   "right_option": "The one that actually looks kind of like herbivore teeth" },
 {   "path_code": '2221',   "prompt": "Columnar cactus types can be tricky to tell apart. Which would you like to see one up close?",   "left_option": "A cactus with many arms and 4 to 6 ribs ",   "center_option": "A cactus with many arms and 9 or 10 ribs ",   "right_option": "A cactus that can have many arms (but sometimes has none!) and 12 to 30 ribs" },
 {   "path_code": '2222',   "prompt": "Barrel and ball growth forms. A rather descriptive category, I think. What would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "A hairy cactus",   "center_option": "A barrel cactus with yellow spines",   "right_option": "A barrel cactus with red or white spines" },
 {   "path_code": '2223',   "prompt": "Here we have cactus varieties that grow paddles. Not useful for rowing, though. Did you find one that you would like to investigate more closely?",   "left_option": "This one has short but wide growth",   "center_option": "This one is tall, like, taller than a person ",   "right_option": "This one is medium sized, shrub-like" },
 {   "path_code": '2231',   "prompt": "Succulent plants with a rosette form and no spines. Very symmetric, and not painful to touch. Lovely plants. Which is loveliest to you?",   "left_option": "The pale pinkish-purple plant",   "center_option": "The plant that looks like it’s covered in spiderwebs",   "right_option": "The plant that gets kinda tree-like" },
 {   "path_code": '2232',   "prompt": "Succulent plants that look like strings of things. These string plants always make me smile. Would you like a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "The one that looks like dolphins",   "center_option": "The one that looks like beads",   "right_option": "The one that looks like bananas" },
 {   "path_code": '2233',   "prompt": "These plants look as if they are made of blades or tongues. Feel free to examine one more closely. What do you think your favorite looks like?",   "left_option": "Looks like tongues",   "center_option": "Looks like propellers… if you squint",   "right_option": "Looks like paddles… or maybe pancakes" },
 {   "path_code": '2311',   "prompt": "The saltwater plants. You know, I’ve heard some gardeners argue about whether kelp was a plant. I think they agreed to disagree. Would you like to look closer at any of these?",   "left_option": "A sweet kelp",   "center_option": "A red kelp",   "right_option": "A giant kelp" },
 {   "path_code": '2312',   "prompt": "Here we have plants that live in freshwater, like ponds and lakes. What would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "A lotus",   "center_option": "A plant with giant floating leaves",   "right_option": "A plant with tiny, frilly leaves" },
 {   "path_code": '2313',   "prompt": "These plants sometimes eat bugs! Bogs are a hard place to live in, after all. Which kind of carnivorous plant would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "A pitcher plant",   "center_option": "A sundew",   "right_option": "A flytrap" },
 {   "path_code": '2321',   "prompt": "European ferns. Lovely plants, these. Which sort of fern would you like to go to?",   "left_option": "A shield-y fern",   "center_option": "A chain-y fern",   "right_option": "A filmy fern" },
 {   "path_code": '2322',   "prompt": "American ferns. Pretty plants. Feel free to examine one more closely.",   "left_option": "Examine a sword-y fern",   "center_option": "Examine a blunt-lobed fern",   "right_option": "Examine a bristly fern" },
 {   "path_code": '2323',   "prompt": "East Asian ferns. Who knew there were so many ferns? Would you like to look more closely at one?",   "left_option": "A beech fern",   "center_option": "A maidenhair fern",   "right_option": "A climbing fern" },
 {   "path_code": '2331',   "prompt": "Here was have corn. Corn kernels can have interestingly different looks and qualities. Would you like to examine any more closely?",   "left_option": "A corn with extra sugars",   "center_option": "A corn with dented kernels",   "right_option": "A corn good for popcorn" },
 {   "path_code": '2332',   "prompt": "Here we have varieties of rice. Rice is one of my favorite grains. It seems to go with everything! Would you like to look more closely at one?",   "left_option": "One with red grains",   "center_option": "One with white grains",   "right_option": "A wild rice" },
 {   "path_code": '2333',   "prompt": "There are three kinds of grains that contain gluten: wheat, barley, and rye. Which would you like to examine more closely?",   "left_option": "A wheat",   "center_option": "A barley",   "right_option": "A rye" },
 {   "path_code": '3111',   "prompt": "I’m always impressed by how many different colors and shapes of tomatoes can be found. Would you like to see one up close?",   "left_option": "A small yellow pear-shaped tomato",   "center_option": "A slicer tomato",   "right_option": "A paste tomato" },
 {   "path_code": '3112',   "prompt": "These potatoes are sorted by the color of the flesh. Feel free to take a closer look at one.",   "left_option": "A potato with yellow flesh",   "center_option": "A potato with purple flesh",   "right_option": "A potato with pink flesh" },
 {   "path_code": '3113',   "prompt": "Eggplants have such a lovely variety of fruit shape and color. Please pick a shape and color to look at.",   "left_option": "Purple and long",   "center_option": "Pinkish purple",   "right_option": "Purple-Black and rotund" },
 {   "path_code": '3121',   "prompt": "Radishes have many uses and many different shapes and colors. What kind of radish interests you?",   "left_option": "A long radish",   "center_option": "A black-skinned radish",   "right_option": "A classic red and round radish" },
 {   "path_code": '3122',   "prompt": "Don’t tell the gardeners, but I can barely tell these turnips apart. Which turnip would you like to examine more closely?",   "left_option": "Turnip with purple on top",   "center_option": "Turnip with yellow skin and flesh",   "right_option": "Turnip with white skin and flesh" },
 {   "path_code": '3123',   "prompt": "Don’t tell the gardeners, but I can barely tell the rutabagas apart. And how are they different from turnips? Anyway, would you like a close look at one?",   "left_option": "The rutabaga with a round-ish root, purple top ",   "center_option": "The rutabaga with an elongated root, purple top ",   "right_option": "The rutabaga with an elongated root, green top" },
 {   "path_code": '3131',   "prompt": "Eating a melon always brings me memories of summer. Would you like a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "A red watermelon",   "center_option": "A yellow watermelon",   "right_option": "A cantaloupe" },
 {   "path_code": '3132',   "prompt": "These squashes come in quite the variety of shapes and sizes. Feel free to examine one more closely.",   "left_option": "A long squash with tan skin",   "center_option": "A squat, round squash with blue skin ",   "right_option": "A long squash with yellow skin" },
 {   "path_code": '3133',   "prompt": "I grew these in my own garden one year and some of them grew as large as a baseball bat! The gardeners here are better gardeners than I. Would you like to see any up close?",   "left_option": "Yellow summer squash with a bent neck",   "center_option": "Long and green summer squash",   "right_option": "Flat-ish summer squash" },
 {   "path_code": '3211',   "prompt": "Do you like figs? There’s quite a variety in the look of the fruit. Would you like to examine one more closely?",   "left_option": "A fig with light yellow-green skin",   "center_option": "A fig with dark purple skin",   "right_option": "A fig with striped yellow green skin" },
 {   "path_code": '3212',   "prompt": "Interesting leaves, interesting foods. Would you like a closer look at one of these nuts?",   "left_option": "A pecan",   "center_option": "A walnut",   "right_option": "A candlenut" },
 {   "path_code": '3213',   "prompt": "All the maple varieties in the garden can be used for maple syrup. Which qualites of a maple are you interested in?",   "left_option": "Harder wood, the sugariest, with 5 lobes on leaves ",   "center_option": "Softer wood, redder leaves in fall ",   "right_option": "Harder wood, darker bark, 3 lobes on leaves" },
 {   "path_code": '3221',   "prompt": "Yum, raspberries. They can grow in so many places and in many colors. Would you like to look at one more closely?",   "left_option": "A black raspberry",   "center_option": "A Hawaiian raspberry",   "right_option": "A red raspberry" },
 {   "path_code": '3222',   "prompt": "Strawberries are such tasty fruit! These plants look so similar on the outside but are quite different on the inside. Which do you fancy?",   "left_option": "A diploid strawberry",   "center_option": "An octoploid strawberry",   "right_option": "A hexaploid strawberry" },
 {   "path_code": '3223',   "prompt": "Some more edible berries. Which do you want to try?",   "left_option": "A black currant",   "center_option": "A blackberry",   "right_option": "A gooseberry" },
 {   "path_code": '3231',   "prompt": "Do you like rose hip tea? I’m quite fond of it. Would you like to examine one of these roses more closely?",   "left_option": "A prairie rose",   "center_option": "A rose with wrinkly leaves",   "right_option": "An interior rose" },
 {   "path_code": '3232',   "prompt": "Grape juice, grape jelly, fresh grapes, and wine. So many ways to enjoy the fruit of these plants. Would you like to examine one more closely?",   "left_option": "A grape native to North America with thick skins and small clusters of fruit",   "center_option": "A grape native to eastern North America",   "right_option": "A grape native to mediterranean area" },
 {   "path_code": '3233',   "prompt": "Hot, cold, fermented… many different ways to use these various plants. Would you like to examine any of these more closely?",   "left_option": "A hibiscus, for tea ",   "center_option": "A flower from a hops, for beer ",   "right_option": "A root from a sassafras, for root beer" },
 {   "path_code": '3311',   "prompt": "These Alocasias all have such lovely leaves. Would you like a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "One with small (for an Alocasia) green leaves",   "center_option": "A night-scented lily",   "right_option": "One that has gray-white veins in the leaves" },
 {   "path_code": '3312',   "prompt": "Some vines are good for swinging on. These are not those kinds of vines. Nonetheless, perhaps you would still like to know more about one of them?",   "left_option": "One with pink-purple flowers shaped like bells",   "center_option": "One with a red flower that has white veining and a distinctive shape",   "right_option": "One with yellow-orange flowers with 5 petals" },
 {   "path_code": '3313',   "prompt": "These trees come from all around the world. Would you like to examine one more closely?",   "left_option": "One native to southern Europe and western Asia",   "center_option": "One native to North America",   "right_option": "One native to East Asia" },
 {   "path_code": '3321',   "prompt": "Most of these are used as landscape trees. They look so strange in this garden though: no branches on any trees here. Which would you like to examine?",   "left_option": "An oak",   "center_option": "A buckeye",   "right_option": "A poplar" },
 {   "path_code": '3322',   "prompt": "Some of these low growers would even try to climb up trees! Would you like to get a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "This one has reddish sap in its roots that can be used as a dye",   "center_option": "This one has blue-violet flowers and can grow in the cracks between rocks",   "right_option": "This one has tiny, white, 5 petaled flowers that appear in a cluster" },
 {   "path_code": '3323',   "prompt": "These shrubs feature distinctive foliage. While valuable for identification, they can also lead people astray when they look similar to other, more famous leaves. Which leaf type would you like to investigate?",   "left_option": "5-lobed leaves that look like a maple leaf ",   "center_option": "Leaves with 7-9 deep lobes",   "right_option": "Leaves with 3-7 shallow lobes" },
 {   "path_code": '3331',   "prompt": "This garden taught me the difference between a leaf and a leaflet. Which traits interest you?",   "left_option": "Native to North America, has large branched thorns on the trunk ",   "center_option": "Native to Asia, has no thorns, has corky bark ",   "right_option": "Native to North America, has short thorns at the base of each leaf" },
 {   "path_code": '3332',   "prompt": "While these plants have some similarity in the leaves, their flower structures are quite different. Would you like a close look at one?",   "left_option": "Has flower spikes with purple-indigo flowers",   "center_option": "A cycad, makes a cone structure ",   "right_option": "Has white flower clusters that turn into white berries" },
 {   "path_code": '3333',   "prompt": "Short plants around here, watch where you step. Lovely flowers. Would you like a closer look at one?",   "left_option": "Reddish purple flowers in a small, dense spike, blooms mid-summer ",   "center_option": "A small ball of purple-pink flowers, blooms mid- to late-summer ",   "right_option": "Drooping flowers, blooming very early spring" }
];

const ROOT_ITEM = BRANCHES.find(x => x.path_code === null);

window.stubPerformFetch = async function(questionCode) {
  if (questionCode.length === 5) {
    const leaf_info = LEAVES.find(x => x.path_code === questionCode);
    return {
        'question_code': leaf_info['path_code'],
        'text_before': leaf_info['prefix_text'].trim(),
        'species_name': leaf_info['species_name'].trim(),
        'text_after': leaf_info['suffix_text'].trim(),
        'image_code': leaf_info['image_code'],
        'type': 'leaf'
    };
  }

  const branch_info = BRANCHES.find(x => x.path_code === questionCode) || ROOT_ITEM;
  return {
      'question_code': branch_info['path_code'],
      'prompt': branch_info['prompt'].trim(),
      'left_option': branch_info['left_option'].trim(),
      'center_option': branch_info['center_option'].trim(),
      'right_option': branch_info['right_option'].trim(),
      'type': 'branch'
  };
};
